For kids, today we are going to start
the day visiting the final fantasy
festival is a festival for fans of
Final Fantasy and they are going to show one today
expansion of the western magician the fifteenth online
which is called and there is also going to be a
lots of merchandising people doing
with their players so they can come back
well be cool so let's go
Let's go inside now because it's so cold today
you shit yourself, partner
[Music]
children of [ __ ] mother
I'm serious, until the event there's a machine
of these to fish things or to be
sick with the game being sick there
tail so you love yourself like a
contest
There are prepared people here, it's a mission
[Laughs]
It's free
[Music]
I think it's an ice cream
she is a lady
the hair we are going to present
and YouTube
[Laughs]
amen
for he did not come out to see our 287 no
further
in a hotel in Kyoto and there is something very
special I want to teach you okay it's a
very popular thing here in Japan to have
some quite unique bathrooms
[Music]
It has opened by itself and all of it comes out
LED lights, okay, this is like the chapter
of the currencies where Japan will visit only
we need music and favorites
so look here there are buttons there are some
nights that I don't know how many here for
wash your little ass to see your juice
that is going down
[Music]
I am
what happens and begins to clarify the
extinction of humanity
[Music]
Well today we are in Kyoto and we are going to
visit one of the geekiest neighborhoods
so to speak, it has everything
It is full of arcades, this one has 10
full of shops and it's called terra match
street is good that there is delicious food and
everything or whatever but it seems like the perfect place
for a virgin like me as well as kids
This is an umbrella shaped like a Qatar.
In the east of Spain they have me with history
I don't think it's normal to carry katanas
on the street in Japan but in Spain I
come with that and shoot me in the
diary but you remember us from last year
he bought a hentai rowlands was
back and there's a whole section of Ruben
angel angel and I getting ready for the
night hard as an angel and I after going
to class later here there are some people there are
mangel alone and asked also alone
games in just here and here we are in
duo want to go look here we are in
squash kid is here they are taking him away
the glasses am angel before making a
book here well don't tell anyone
but I'm going to take this to take this
house for scientific topics for
study Japanese culture and that god
My boy, this is the ultimate machine.
to end all the tacos
world
[Music]
there were men's programs
This is a Christian arcade in Japan.
I know the time for fights anywhere
They gut you, I think I've already mentioned it.
many times but today we have finally
found one
[Music]
this is a paper
but
It's nothing special but it's Japanese and the
people throw things away, they have no feelings
poor trash can remember her this is her
unique and special in Japan there is no
waste bins
If you ever travel there remember that no
there are trash cans
if they carried
burning
[Music]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
vivo
[Applause]
i
[Music]
[Applause]